http://www.ljrelite.com/privacy-policy/

Lady Jean Ranch, Inc.
Menu
Privacy Policy
Legal Statement
These policies relate to information that we at Lady Jean Ranch gather about you and the use that we make of it in the course of our business. Your use of this website shows your acceptance of these terms.
Lady Jean Ranch may collect personally identifying information during contest, sweepstakes, commerce transactions and site membership registration. Such information includes:
Name
Address
Gender
Age
Email
Phone number
Social media identifiers
Credit card number (for commerce transactions)
In addition, information is collected in certain portions of the site in which guests specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, contact forms, community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions or voting. Lady Jean Ranch may use such information for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when guests provide the information).
By submitting an email address through a contact form, you consent to receive correspondence as it pertains to your inquiry. In addition, your email address will be added to a database for future marketing efforts. You may opt-out at any time by emailing us or by written request to:
Lady Jean Ranch
10333 Randolph Siding Road
Jupiter, FL 33478
Lady Jean Ranch Generally Avoids Sharing Information With Third Parties
Lady Jean Ranch may share Information with third party service providers it employs to perform functions and provide services for you and the website, subject to the terms of this policy, and only to the extent necessary to process payments; to prevent, detect, and investigate fraud or other prohibited activities; to facilitate dispute resolution, such as chargebacks or refunds; and for other purposes associated with the acceptance of credit or debit cards.
Lady Jean Ranch may share your credit or debit card numbers with third party payment services providers or card networks, only to the extent necessary to monitor card transactions at participating merchants and track redemption activity for the purposes of providing card-linked services.
Additionally, Lady Jean Ranch will share data with Google pursuant to Google’s privacy policy for Google Analytics, found at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/
Policies For Individuals 16 And Under
No information should be submitted to or posted on Lady Jean Ranch by children 16 years of age or under without their parent's or guardian's consent. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection.
Although children are allowed to participate in contests, children ages 16 and under must get their parent's or guardian's permission before entering any sweepstakes or contests. No information collected from children 16 years of age or under is used by Lady Jean Ranch for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Lady Jean Ranch.
Policies For Individuals Over 16 Years Of Age
Information submitted at the time of any form of registration by a guest who is over 16 years of age may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Lady Jean Ranch. Lady Jean Ranch does not share this information with other companies. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use at any time by written request. The request should be sent to us at:
Lady Jean Ranch
10333 Randolph Siding Road
Jupiter, FL 33478
Use Of Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier by saving your passwords, purchases and preferences. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major Web sites.
Lady Jean Ranch does not share information with any third parties whatsoever. Lady Jean Ranch does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie.
Cookies help make Lady Jean Ranch better by showing how and when guests use the site. Many content improvements and updates are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This statistical information is most easily tracked with cookies.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, it is possible that some areas of the site will not function properly if you do so.
Additionally, Lady Jean Ranch will collect and share cookie data with Google pursuant to Google’s privacy policy for Google Analytics, found at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
Lady Jean Ranch reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying guests of the existence of a new privacy policy. Reasonable notice of changes will be posted on our website. Updated privacy policies will be posted at http://dauphinaisconcrete.com/privacy/ and will govern immediately after public posting. Continued use of the Lady Jean Ranch after notice of the changes has been posted to the website will be deemed acceptance of the changes, regardless of whether you actually reviewed the changes. You can send mail with any further questions to us at:
Lady Jean Ranch
10333 Randolph Siding Road
Jupiter, FL 33478
Review And Change Personally Identifying Information
Lady Jean Ranch does not maintain a way at this time for previously stored personally identifying information to be reviewed or changed by a user.
Do Not Track
Lady Jean Ranch does not presently honor do not track requests but does not interfere with Google Analytics’ policies with respect to such requests.
Third Party Website Tracking
Lady Jean Ranch does not share its customer’s data submitted through this website with third parties, nor does it acquire data from third parties for the purpose of tracking users of this website, except to the extent done so by Google Analytics.
Lady Jean Ranch, Inc.
10333 Randolph Siding RoadJupiter, Florida 33478P: (561) 745-1300
Equestrian Boarding
Weddings
Corporate / Special Events
Venue Map
The Tree House
About Us
Agritourism
Contact Us
Testimonials
“Beautiful equestrian and event facility! The large covered arena is perfect for all weather conditions... premier stables, paddocks, and exercise tracks. Triple AAA.”
–Corinne M.
“A beautiful facility filled with wonderful and considerate people!”
–Joanna C.
© 2018–Present, Lady Jean Ranch, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
